{
    "name": "Test Name",
    "subject": "English",
    "response": [
        {
            "question": "He did not give up fight even though he was badly bruised.",
            "a": "The fight did not give up by him even though he was badly bruised.",
            "b": "The fight had not given up by him even though he was badly bruised",
            "c": "The fight was not given up by him even though he was badly bruised",
            "d": "The fight was not being given up by him even though he was badly bruised",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should avoid tranquilizer in order to have a good health",
            "a": "Tranquilizer should avoided by us in order to have good health.",
            "b": "Tranquilizer should been avoided by us in order to have a good health. ",
            "c": "Tranquilizer should be avoid by us in order to have a good health.",
            "d": "Tranquilizer should be avoided by us in order to have a good health.",

            "correct": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His wife upbraided him for his irresponsible handling of family finance.",
           "a":" He upbraided by his wife for his irresponsible handling of the family finance." ,
            "b":"He has upbraided by his wife for his irresponsible handling of the family finance.",
            "c":"He were upbraided by his wife for his irresponsible handling of the family finance.",
            "d":"He were upbraided by his wife for his irresponsible handling of the family finance.",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She never understood me, whenever I said something."
,
            "a": "Whenever I said something, I never understood by her.",
            "b": "Whenever I said something, I had never understood by her.",
            "c": "Whenever I said something, I was being never understood by her.",
            "d": "Whenever I said something I was never understood by her.",
            "correct": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I am alone, I hear footsteps of my friend in my imagination."
,
            "a": "The footsteps of my friend is heard by me when I am alone.",
            "b": "The footsteps of my friend are heard by me when I am alone.",
            "c": "The footsteps of my friend was heard by me when I am alone.",
            "d": "The footsteps of my friend was heard by me when I am alone.",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You need not come unless you want to.",
            "a": "You don't need to come unless you want to",
            "b": "You come only when you want to  ",
            "c": "You come unless you don't want to",
            "d": "You come unless you don't want to",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man to who I sold my house was a cheat.",
            "a": "to whom I sell",
            "b": "who was sold to",
            "c": "No correction required ",
            "d": "to whom I sold",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were all shocked at his failure in the competition. ",
            "a": "were shocked at all",
            "b": "had all shocked at",
            "c": "had been all shocked on",
            "d": "No correction required",
            "correct": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were all shocked at his failure in the competition.",
            "a": "were shocked at all",
            "b": "had all shocked at",
            "c": "had all shocked by",
            "d": "had all shocked for",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The population of Tokyo is greater than that of any other town in the world.",
            "a": "greatest among any other",
            "b": "greater than all other",
            "c": "greater than those of any other",
            "d": "greater than those of any other",
            "correct": "d"
        }
    ]
}